It's very difficult to explain the role
in one word, but I played a woman
named Kei, but she's a vampire, and
this time there are two types of vampires.
A new vampire called Neo
Vampire and an old vampire.
It's a story where the
two are in conflict, but I'm
a vampire from the beginning,
and I'm a strong woman.
It's very difficult to explain.
I'll say one more thing, but Japanese
people mix Dracula and vampires.
Director Sion Sono
That's right.
I didn't know that Dracula and
vampires were completely different.
Not all people in Sengoku
era say Oda Nobunaga,
but people in Oda Nobunaga
say Dracula is Dracula.
So Dracula is a family.
It's different from a normal vampire, so
it's not well known that heroes are right.
That's right.
Dracula is completely
different from vampires.
Heroes are right.
I'm a vampire, not a Dracula.
I'm going to fight.
ABB, count 23.
Onward!
Ready!
Start!
ABB.
Check!
This is the Tokyo Vampire Hotel.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yami Tomita, and I play Manami.
Manami was born with a very precious blood.
She lived as a normal girl for 21 years.
When she turned 22, she
was awakened for the first time.
She lived as a normal girl until then, but
she was suddenly told about her identity.
She was overwhelmed by fate.
I play Manami.
The sky is very dangerous.
When I went to the Fujiya Hotel last year,
I thought it would be interesting if
all the hotel owners were vampires.
After that, I was invited to
the Transylvania Film Festival.
At that time, I tried to do all
the films I had done so far.
At that time, I loved Dracula.
All the places in Transylvania that
were related to Dracula were filmed.
It wasn't filmed, but it was filmed.
There was a cave under the hotel.
I thought about the idea of
living there as a human being.
That's why I made this film.
I'll suck up all your power.
It was a lot harder than
I've ever experienced.
I always talked to the pumpkin.
It was a long time.
This time, I was in charge of
filming in Romania for 10 days.
We started filming in about three months.
A lot of things happened
during the three months of filming.
I've only seen the first three episodes.
When I saw it, I was so happy.
Really?
I thought, this is how it's done.
I didn't have time to look
at the monitor during filming.
I was moved when I
saw it for the first time.
What was the name of the place in the cave?
Sarinator.
It was an amusement park.
There was a Ferris wheel in the basement.
It wasn't that much of an amusement park.
But it was a place where
people dug up salt and made coal.
Unlike coal, people never died.
It was a place where
everyone was happy in history.
The people who dug up
the salt became healthier.
Because they bathed in salt
every day, their skin was shiny.
It was the best place.
It was also used for early treatment.
Everyone who worked
there lived a long life.
I heard you were sick.
But I caught a cold.
We caught a cold.
It's been a while since
we went to Sarinator.
I couldn't stop sneezing.
It's become a habit.
I heard you came back
from Romania with a cold.
No, I didn't.
It's a joke, isn't it?
It was hell for the staff in Romania.
It was more difficult than for the actors.
The assistant director, who had a
lot of experience, came from Japan.
But she was crying because it was
the hardest thing she had ever done.
It was that hard.
Especially in the cave,
there were a lot of stairs.
The underground was really deep.
The staff climbed it over and over again.
I climbed it over and over again.
For example, the Sunshine Building.
It was so scary that I had
to do it over and over again.
That's how scary it was.
Did you speak Romanian?
Yes, I did.
At first, I was told that I couldn't do it.
I was told that on the first or second day.
But I got better quickly.
It was great.
It was difficult.
It's a language I've never heard before.
There were a lot of Romanian lines.
I had a hard time memorizing it.
I heard that the locals were also Romanian.
That's what I heard.
I was really moved when I first saw it.
I was especially moved by the entrance.
You should have made a better set.
But it was great.
It was great.
The hotel rooms were also well-made.
The colors of the rooms were amazing.
The rooms were blue and yellow.
If I had to choose, I would definitely
choose a hotel room with no colors.
I couldn't imagine how much it would cost.
I couldn't afford it.
That's what I thought.
I wanted to do more in terms of art.
But I could do it in terms of acting.
I couldn't do it in terms
of Japanese scenery.
The reality of Japanese scenery is amazing.
So I couldn't show
the exterior of the hotel.
If I did that, the exterior of the hotel
would be overshadowed by Japanese scenery.
Then the reality would be boring.
Let's start with the balcony frame.
When I was asked to act as Manami,
I was asked to act as Bozu.
I was surprised.
But the scene where the wig was
taken at the bar was very interesting.
It was a shocking scene even for me.
As a result, I was glad to act as Bozu.
Mr. Sono also acted
as Bozu on the first day.
On the first day when I
was asked to act as Bozu.
The real thing.
Hurry up.
I'm going to show my
love for Ami with my hair.
It's a hair-style.
I was trying to act as Bozu.
Then I caught a cold.
I was cold and my head was...
I was cold and my head was Bozu.
Are you okay?
I acted as Bozu on the first day.
You can't fail.
Of course I can't fail.
It was my first time to act as Bozu.
I don't think I'll do it again in my life.
I wanted to act as Bozu on the first day.
I was surprised.
I was motivated.
How many people died in just a
few minutes of the first episode?
A lot of people died in just one episode.
You've never played such an
intense role before, have you?
No, it's my first time.
You killed a lot of people in an hour.
I killed a lot of people.
Some people were beaten up.
That's right.
I think there were a lot of memorable
episodes during the shooting.
That's right.
I did a lot of things.
I had to follow the order
from the first episode.
Every day.
I was obviously tired in the second half.
That's right.
I couldn't get up at the end.
I didn't have much time to sleep.
The filming of the climax
of the movie was intense.
I've always wanted to
shoot a vampire movie.
I didn't think it would be this hard.
It was hard.
It was a sea of blood in the second half.
A lot of staff members fell and slipped.
I don't remember much about the shooting.
I didn't know what would happen to
me and Kei at the end of the 7th episode.
I didn't know until just
before the shooting.
I didn't write it in the script.
We talked about what would
happen to us in the middle of the night.
I was worried about what would happen.
I don't know when the shooting will end.
I couldn't see the end.
I was really worried.
At first, I was shooting
until the 5th episode.
After that, I wrote that I was fighting.
I didn't know what would happen.
If the human team dies
once, it's all up there.
Everyone was so nervous.
I didn't know where the order was.
I was wondering when I was going to die.
I've been hit in the face many times.
I've been hit many times.
Have you ever done a
landing scene like that?
It's my first time.
It's your first time?
Yes, it's my first time.
How many times did you get hit?
It must have hurt a lot.
I landed in the middle of Toyohashi.
I was really desperate.
Was it cold there?
It was still cold.
It was around the beginning of November.
I drank a lot when I went
to Toyohashi for three days.
I ate a lot.
I didn't think I would be a sniper.
I've been through that a lot.
You can't do that kind
of shooting in Japan.
In Japan, you can't do that.
You can't shoot in a shopping district.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was really hard.
I didn't have much time to practice.
The setting was strong.
I used a gun and a sword.
It's a unique action
I've never seen before.
It was really hard.
I can't help it.
I have to do it.
Kao is...
I think it's because it's a hard role.
Kao is a completely different person.
I was surprised.
But I was really happy to
be invited to his work again.
That's why I'm...
You've come to the end.
I've come to the end.
That's why I'm here now.
I was tired.
I was like, do your best.
It was really hard.
It's good to see a man
and a woman fighting.
It's rare.
It's my first time doing an action.
It's really good.
Manami's action is...
I'm going to wake up and become a beast.
It's a vampire, but it's a beast.
The script says beast.
I thought it was an animal.
It's not a very polite action.
It's an action that kills people.
It's an action that takes a lot of energy.
The wire was my first challenge.
It was hard.
It's not a very good action.
As for the action,
It wasn't that hard.
I've lost my human heart.
To be honest, I don't remember
when I woke up as a vampire.
I don't know if I won or lost.
I don't know what I did.
I don't remember.
It's okay.
Now,
With this scene,
It's all up.
Thank you for your hard work.
One more time.
Okay.
In a word, this work...
It's hard to see.
But I've never experienced
this scene before.
It's a really amazing scene.
I've only seen the first three episodes.
I've never seen this before.
It was a really shocking work.
Mr. Matsumoto is
shooting an original drama.
Romania shooting,
And a gorgeous set, action.
I think it's a drama that's
never been done in Japan.
I think you'll enjoy it.
It's a fierce action scene.
It's a vampire vs. human fight.
There's a lot of things I can't say here.
From the first episode to
the third and fourth episodes,
Kei, who played Kago-chan,
Manami, who played me.
I think it's one of the
highlights of how it changes.
The cast, including Mr. Kago,
Mr. Sonoshino,
It's a work that we
all made with our lives.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
I hope this will be an opportunity.
I hope it will be an opportunity for
Japanese net dramas to be interesting.
Please watch Tokyo Vampire Hotel.
Here we go.
Okay.
Thank you very much.